We'll be right back.
A mysterious man appears?
His name is Sniper King.
What the hell is he doing over there?
Come on.
Just humor the poor guy.
He has too much pride to show his face to the crew, but he still wants to rescue his friend.
Who knows what secrets hide behind him.
Well, long as he stops singing, I guess.
Hey, get over here!
Oh, sure.
Hey, let's start the meeting for Operation Rescue Robin.
We've never met before.
Don't you two have any questions about me?
So, the car you were in was car number six.
That means that we've got five more left.
You know, like, where's Sniper Island?
But we don't know which one of those Robin is in.
The answer is, it's in your heart.
And by the way, are you strong?
Are you kidding?
I'm super strong.
Even stronger than usual this week.
Remember, the point is to rescue Robin, not beat the enemy.
At least in theory.
We're up against a lot of Marines in a narrow space, so we've got to make sure we don't
get surrounded.
We should avoid as many fights as we can and whittle down the main force in turns.
Makes sense to me.
Even though we're total strangers, my intuition tells me that I can trust your judgment.
With that in mind, I have a plan.
Oh.
Here we go.
Listen up.
Am I dreaming?
It's a miracle.
Okay.
Now I'm ready for battle.
What's going on?
Don't you play innocent with me, immoral girl.
Have you no shame changing your clothes out here in front of everyone?
Shame is overrated.
What was I supposed to do?
The train only has one car.
Cover up your legs.
Cover up your stomach.
That goes for you too, square-hand sisters.
People like you are corrupting society.
Whatever.
You're just too shy.
Shy boy.
Why you?
If you fellas like, I could change too.
Please.
Anything but that.
We promise we'll be hay.
If you don't like mature women, it's your law.
Stupid black shorts with their stupid tiny pockets.
Come on.
Get in there.
Don't put meat in your pants, you idiot.
I started to think you might actually pull this off.
You certainly seem riled up, if nothing else.
You bet we are.
Those jerks got away with Robin last time, but now that I know what's going on, they don't
stand a chance.
I hope you're right.
Because if you get stuck in something again, you're going to have hell to pay.
Nah, don't worry.
I got a reason to beat them this time around.
Uh, right.
Hey, did you change your weapon, Nami?
Oh, no.
It's pretty much the same one as before.
Usopp just improved it with some dials after we got back from Skypiea.
This is the perfect climate act.
I see.
So that's his...
Right.
It's Usopp's, uh, last work.
Don't get all sad now!
You ready?
Let's do this.
An intruder?
Uh, yes, sir.
That's what I heard.
It's not feasible to board the Puffing Tom while it's running.
If there really is an intruder, that means we let him sneak on board before we departed.
What an embarrassment.
Tackoo!
I agree, sir.
It's inexcusable.
But if you can't get on while the train is moving, you can't get off either.
That means the intruder, as well as the missing prisoners, are still here somewhere.
You just have to find them.
Captain T-Bone, I don't think there's any room for someone to hide in here.
Huh?
Good evening.
It's them!
They were right outside!
We found three suspicious men, including the criminals in car seven!
Corner and capture them!
Ever use a hammer before?
Because you sure do suck.
Shut up!
There's no point in resisting!
Open the door already!
They're gonna break through!
I know.
Go!
This way!
They found the intruder in car seven!
The criminals too?
Yeah.
Let the guys in car three know.
That Frankie guy's a lot of trouble.
Move in and capture them alive!
Move it!
Stand back!
Whoa!
They're shooting at us!
Then hurry it up!
A little help would be nice!
Don't shoot blindly!
We don't want these guys dead!
You're right.
What do we do, Captain T-Bone?
Allow me to handle this.
I hate crooked men and crooked swordplay.
Here comes my right-angle flash!
BORDSWA!
What?
Where is the
Nightingale!
I hate crooked men and crooked swordplay.
Here comes my right-angle flash!
Bordeswar!
They're gone!
The roof?
Girls, they're at the end of the train!
Now, hurry!
Oh, no!
Everyone get back to the front cars right now!
This is a trap!
What are you talking about?
What the?
Quick! Retreat! They tricked us!
Huh?
We can't go back anymore! The door's blocked!
No way!
The cars are detached!
Whoa!
Damn it!
That's cheating!
You'll pay for this!
I was too late.
Have a safe trip, gentlemen!
Say hello to the Sea Kings for me!
Fare thee well!
That's two cars down.
Should cut the small fries down by about 50 or so.
But aren't Luffy and the others coming on the same railway?
What happens when the cars run into each other?
Eh, they'll come up with something.
Huh?
You arrogant thugs!
I'm gonna chair this door down and you with it!
Ah!
Oh, going for a swim?
All right.
Five to go.
You bastard!
You're gonna suffer for that one!
What will poor Captain Tebow do?
Hey!
Report this to CP-9!
Great.
More of these guys.
Ah!
And Freight, SRT!
Sniper King!
Gun Potter Star!
Ah!
Strong right!
Heavyweight shot!
Fire!
Ah!
They hit him!
That hurt.
Keep shooting!
Why isn't the gun working on him?!
Ah!
Oh, that was crazy.
What the hell are you?
Ah!
Oh!
Guess I forgot to tell you.
I'm a cyborg!
Those are real?!
Yep!
I got stealing weapons built right into my body.
Still kinda hurts if I get shot.
I might bleed a little too.
But no big deal.
Just when you think you've seen it all.
The world's a crazy place.
Awesome!
Poke.
Ah!
What in the hell was that for?!
Huh?
You can deflect bullets, but needles hurt?
For one, I'm not your science experiment, so stop poking me!
And for two, just so you know, my back isn't the same as my front, get it?
I had to do the operation on myself, so I couldn't reach around behind me.
In other words, only the front side is cyborg.
I see.
While I'm at it, let me tell you another little secret.
My belly's always cold.
Can you guess why?
How would I know?
It's cause I got my own personal fridge in there to keep my cola cold.
Wow, that's handy.
Man, that's gotta be great in the summer!
Okay, the cola thing is really neat, but we don't have time for this.
We gotta get moving to the next car.
This one is number four.
Huh?
I'm Wonsy!
It's a mad, mad, mad, mad world, and I'm a mad, mad, mad, mad Wonsy!
Let us read something else.
It is untrenched...
What will continue doing at night that he negotiations
Even if I smile and I'll be Guelect
anymore, I don't like the enemy
I'll have to carry over
How do you like my Mad Mad Ramen Kenpo? Pretty crazy, huh?
I hate people who play with their food.
If you're going to talk saucy, you better bring your cooking skills.
It's not like me to use my hands, but since this is a kitchen battle,
I'll make an exception and show you how a real chef handles his knives.
On the next, One Piece, showdown between cooks, Sanji versus Ramen Kenpo.
I'm going to be king of the pirates.